[♪ hip-hop playing]
The bass is money.
Sounds like somebody's barbecue
got shut down by the cops.
[♪ hip-hop playing]
[softly] Huh?
Fuck, no.
Wack.
[inhales deeply] Okay.
[exhales]
[♪ hip-hop playing]
Yeah.
♪♪ So what... ♪
This is it, Tillery.
♪♪ You find out my name
Is Artillery ♪
♪♪ Is that a threat? ♪
♪♪ Depends on who's asking ♪
♪♪ Oh, shit, Little Demon start
Blasting pop, pop, pop ♪
[tires screeching]
♪ Pop-pop to the leg
One shot, hit him dead
In the head ♪
[♪ song continues]
♪♪ Should I stay
Or should I run? ♪
♪♪ Officer down
Heeded some help from a nigga
He was tryin' to stun ♪
♪♪ Oh, ain't this
A predicament? ♪
[♪ song continues]
♪♪ You ain't a Black man
Don't ever forget it ♪
♪ So, what, you a cop
You still die like a ni... ♪
[music stops]
[buzzing, beeping]
So how we looking, Mr. Kinsey?
[Mr. Kinsey exhales deeply]
Well, I used the Isky cam
on the rebuild,
so don't start complaining
now that Edelbrock
is stalling 'cause that...
that thump,
that whoop-whoop, it's just
a little too deep on the idle.
It's all good, Mr. Kinsey.
I know you're gonna have
that thing sounding right.
- James.
- Hey, start it up.
- [engine starts]
- [James] All right.
[♪ hip-hop plays]
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna kill 'em on the show
when this thing done, man.
You're the best, Mr. Kinsey.
For real.
Yeah, you got that right.
♪♪ Yep, that's the name
Of my hometown
I'm throwing down in the town ♪
♪♪ With my name is all around ♪
- Damn, that shit fucked up.
- [friend chuckles]
[scoffs] Hey, Wanda,
- I see you ready
for the cars show.
- [chuckles]
I see you ready
for the world with that damn
curl grease dripping.
[friends laughing]
No, I promise, Ms. Judy,
you've gotta stop competing
with the sisters
at Victory Baptist,
or we'll never get started.
We can table it.
I'll let you deal
with your niece.
Hey, dear.
Hey, Ms. Judy.
All right.
I swear, there'll
be peace in the streets
before there's peace
between Victory Baptist
and those mean old
stormtroopers, girl.
You're here for your cousin?
And some biscuits and homemade
jam if there's any left.
Lamar.
[♪ hip-hop playing]
He wants to play you
his new tracks. That's what
he wants me to call 'em now.
Can y'all stop?
I mean, he's 19,
and he's a grown man,
but please, Wanda, do not
encourage the rap dreams.
I mean, that damn music bug.
It's not your fault.
- That boy's first words
were Quincy Jones.
- Yeah.
James Sr. gave it to his
mother, who gave it to James.
I just hope Lamar's got
more sense than you did.
I'll beat his ass.
My bad, Mama G.
Hey, Wanda, guess who
bringing me and Big Daddy
a Chevy to work on later.
Who?
Leon.
You better not, punk.
- [James chuckles]
- [Wanda] I'm serious, James.
Last thing I need is some
grown man standing over
an engine block or whatever,
gossiping about us
getting back together.
[chuckles] Well,
y'all make up and break up
more than Tom and Jerry.
- Can you blame him?
- It's for real this time.
[Mama G] Lamar,
your cousin's waiting on you.
Now, James, do not change
out those clothes before you go
to the recruiter, y'hear?
- Aight.
- [Big Daddy] Look sharp, right?
- You hear me?
- Yes, sir.
[Big Daddy]
And I left that alternator out.
Blue mark five
sitting back there.
[James] All right, I got you.
[Wanda] Lamar, let's go!
[music stops]
- What's up, cuz?
- What's up?
- Hey.
- [sighs]
Heard you got some shit
to play me.
I always got some shit
to play you.
Pop that shit in.
But wait, I gotta pretend
I don't like it.
Mama Gerty said that?
They mean the best.
Whole city's on fire right now.
Plus your brother is somebody,
so I get why they're
overprotective.
No, they wanna shrink me
into nothing, plant me
in that church band.
If you shrink, that's on you.
Let's hear it.
[♪ atmospheric hip-hop playing]
- A city-wide emergency...
- ...in Los Angeles
for rock cocaine.
...for the murders
of over 100...
Over 40 uniformed officers
over the fatal...
539 gang-related murders...
...friends after a short life
in a dangerous game...
Affecting the current murder rate.
Another seemingly
random shooting.
Has been the site
of multiple drive-by shootings.
The jump in violent crimes.
Officers in the
Rodney King beatings were found
not guilty on all counts.
Shooting that claimed
over eight lives.
[chatter continues, faint]
[♪ music continues]
[tape rewinding]
[♪ music stops]
Man...
[chuckles] It's fucking good!
[laughing]
I don't know what to say
except it sounded like LA.
You've been saying
DG needs producers.
You think you could
get this to him?
[exhales] Negro...
[chuckles]
[♪ uplifting music plays]
[Wanda]
I'm not a used car salesman.
I work in the music business.
This car shit is temporary.
Look, I heard
your niece's demo,
and I've been making some moves
in the music biz with DG.
You probably know him
from the car shows.
Wanda, are you serious?
Sorry, Mr. Preston.
Big Daddy's name
only go so far with me.
And she's back.
Close it.
[Wanda] Trinice...
Looking good. [chuckles]
Girl, get in your car.
I don't know, Wanda.
I promised Donny I'd wait
till he gets here first.
It costs you nothing
to sit in it.
[Trinice chuckles]
[sighs]
Touch up your lip gloss.
- What?
- Touch up your lip gloss.
Look at those lips hittin',
just like these ladies.
[chuckles]
Okay, we got AC, low mileage
and the Alpine sound system.
Look, the previous owner
left his tape.
It's gotta be a sign.
[both chuckle]
[♪ "Cutie Pie" playing]
Imagine everyone's out cruising
the shore on a Saturday night,
and you pull up in this.
Top down, cake from Miko's,
hair whip, biker shorts.
You telling me
every head won't turn?
Especially when you
pull up pumping this.
[imitates song melody]
[Trinice imitates song melody]
[both laughing]
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
♪♪ Cutie pie ♪
♪♪ You're the reason why ♪
♪♪ I love you so ♪
♪♪ I don't want you to go ♪
[♪ music stops]
Fuck it.
I'm in.
All right. [chuckles]
- [exhales]
- You know, you really
had me going, girl.
That's 'cause
you know I'm right.
[both chuckle]
Okay.
Eleven grand.
Congrats.
[♪ "Life Is... Too Short"
playing]
♪♪ Take back
All the things you give ♪
Hell yeah, baby girl.
[both chuckle]
[Donny] Hell yeah!
We're gonna kill it pulling up
with something like this.
[Trinice] Mm-hmm.
This is my girl, Wanda,
I've been telling you about.
Wanda.
Nah, we out.
- But...
- Let's go.
It's a great car.
♪♪ No time to waste
Just get on that case ♪
[Donny] She's a crackhead.
The car probably
is busted as shit.
♪♪ Livin' like a king
On a throne ♪
♪♪ Getting everything you want
And trying to handle your own ♪
♪♪ It's your life
Don't be stupid though ♪
♪♪ 'Cause when you waste it
You'll know life is... ♪
[music stops]
[♪ hip-hop playing]
[Lamar] It's LA.
The sweetness of sunshine.
Beaches, fine-ass women.
But you notice something
more sinister is lurking
underneath the... the surface.
Like Five... Five-O coming
to funk with your hood.
[store worker] Man, cuz,
why every conversation
gotta be weird
with that retarded
Mork from Ork shit?
Hey, come on, man.
What?
Y'all don't think it's good?
Y'all keep pampering this boy,
on crip.
He gonna starve in the wild.
We're raising him like a bitch.
Even James gave it up
for this one.
Your brother don't know shit
about music. What he do
know about is pow, pow!
Shut your ass up, Skip.
You ain't liked a new song
since 1973.
- [chuckles]
- [Skip] Fuck y'all.
[giggles]
[♪ jazz music plays]
Arsene, can you check
and see if that Five Sharps
from Sweden came in?
- The 78?
- Yeah.
[bell rings]
[Lamar]
Damn, it's 3:00 already?
Fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
You'll be fine. Beaumont House
doesn't let out until 3:15.
Just do not get on the 108.
Seriously, the city
is hot right now.
Take the 40 West.
It's gonna cost you
a couple of hours,
but you will avoid those tower
Crips from Leimert High.
"I don't bang"
ain't gon' work right now.
[softly] I know, I know.
Sit at the front of the bus.
[♪ "M.A.A.D. City"
(Feat. MC Eiht) playing]
You okay, sweetheart?
I'm-I'm fine.
[horn honking]
Come on, man.
What you want me to do?
Hey. Hey, homie.
Where you from?
What you looking around for, homie?
Oh, you heard us, cuz.
Where you from?
- Hey, hey.
- [person 1] Dude,
them fools right there.
Hey, you little nigga.
[horn honking]
- [person 2] Oh, shit!
- [person 3] What the hell
was that?
[person 2] Hell, no!
Smoke him!
♪♪ Yawk! Yawk! Yawk! Yawk! ♪
♪♪ Man down
Where you from, nigga? ♪
♪ Fuck who you know
Where you from, my nigga? ♪
♪♪ Where your grandma stay
Huh, my nigga? ♪
♪♪ This m.A.A.d city I run... ♪
All right. Come on, come on.
Go, go!
[♪ music stops]
[panting]
[♪ ominous music plays]
[♪ "M.A.A.D. City"
(Feat. MC Eiht) continues]
♪♪ This is not a rap on how
I'm slingin' crack
Or move cocaine ♪
♪♪ This is cul-de-sac
And plenty Cognac
And major pain ♪
♪♪ Not the drill sergeant
But the stress
That weighing on your brain ♪
[passenger] Hey, homie.
You in the front.
I know you hear us.
I'm talking to you.
Where you from?
At this light, I'm gonna give
you a head start, all right?
Don't run! Let's get him!
Let's get him!
Go!
♪♪ Seen a light-skinned nigga
With his brains blown out ♪
♪♪ At the same burger stand
Where... [bleep] ...hang out ♪
♪♪ Now this is
Not a tape recording
Saying that he did it ♪
♪♪ But ever since that day
I was lookin' at him
Different ♪
♪♪ That was back when I was nine
Joey packed the nine ♪
♪♪ Pakistan on every porch
Is fine ♪
- [whistles]
- [clamoring, shouting]
♪♪ With the sliding door
Fuck is up? ♪
♪♪ Fuck you shootin' for if you
Ain't walkin' up
You fuckin' punk? ♪
Shit.
♪♪ Pickin' off you suckers
Suck a dick or die
Or sucker punch ♪
♪♪ A wall of bullets
Comin' from ♪
♪♪ AK's, AR's
"Aye y'all, duck" ♪
♪♪ That's what momma said
When we was eatin'
That free lunch ♪
♪♪ Aw, man, goddamn
All hell broke loose ♪
♪♪ You killed my cousin
Back in '94
Fuck yo' truce ♪
[panting]
[♪ music stops]
[♪ "Keep Takin' Me Back"
playing]
♪♪ Keep takin' me back ♪
♪♪ So many times I fall ♪
[passenger 1] Man, fuck!
[passenger 2]
Where did he go, cuz?
[passengers speak indistinctly]
♪♪ Keep takin' me back ♪
[gulps, sighs]
[♪ music stops]
[inhales] You was crying?
- [smacks thigh]
- Let's go, bro.
You know,
if they would have hurt you,
we would have burnt
that whole block down, right?
You gotta tighten up more.
Like, that shit back there
cannot fucking happen.
What you gonna do
when I'm not around, cuz?
I-I've been thinking
about that,
and I-I think that
we have to just ask Big Daddy
for more time.
Nigga, I'm not you.
If I even asked to-to breathe
more air around here,
Big Daddy liable
to kick me out.
Well, you can't try?
I've been doing everything.
I've been sending tapes
to labels, to managers.
I mean, Pastor Rodney,
didn't he say that my mission
is ordained?
[back seat passenger]
Shit, nigga. For 10%,
Pastor Rodney will tell you
you can fly, cuz.
Man, can y'all stop for once?
So-So what?
We can't do shit around here
but drink forties and wear
matching clothes to funerals?
[James]
You're not Wanda, nigga.
You ain't got no goddamn
business in the rap game.
So before Big Daddy go bad
on all three of us,
just join the band
at First AME.
All right, just get some money
in your pocket.
All right? Man the fuck up.
Cuz. [chuckles]
I think your robot
short-circuited. [chuckling]
[♪ somber music playing]
[growling]
Hey.
[chuckles] Hey.
Hey, hey. Come here.
Aw. [chuckles]
[chuckles]
[breathes heavily]
Goddamn it, Wanda,
what the fuck are you doing?
I knocked first.
Besides, you're the one
who made me give back the key.
Yeah, you're fucking right,
because you moved out.
Only reason you ain't dead
'cause the dogs wasn't barking
when I came home.
Thank you, Bunchy.
Thank you, Carter.
You gonna shoot me, Lee?
[chuckles]
This shit ain't
fucking funny, all right?
I almost popped your ass.
You sneaking up,
climbing through windows
and shit like back
when you was on that shit.
Breaking and entering
for a goddamn record?
[sighs] For a goddamn sample.
But if you had
a drop of creativity,
you understand inspiration
hits when it hits.
But I guess if you knew that,
I'd still have the keys, right?
[scoffs]
Here you go with that shit.
[sighs]
Look, I'm sorry.
I gotta wake up early to go
to the legal clinic, so...
You wanna stay?
I don't think
that's a good idea, Leon.
[sighs]
[Gerty inhales, exhales]
[♪ soul music playing]
[person 4] DG,
I wouldn't be doing my job if
I didn't bring these things up.
I absolutely did not say
let me leave the meeting.
What I said was,
"This place is in trouble, all
of their bands are crashing,
be careful with Jenny."
That's what I said.
Oh. Well, is that 'cause
she's white or 'cause
you wanna fuck her? [chuckles]
That's funny.
You're mean when you don't
need me to pay off a judge.
Oh.
Look, this bitch
set up this meeting 'cause
she needs to bust a move.
Come on!
[♪ hip-hop playing]
Okay.
This is what crosses over,
clubs, radio, MTV, all that.
I'm telling you, Jenny.
[♪ music ends]
[Jenny] Feels familiar.
[Darryl]
That's exactly the point.
Not the right one.
Listen, Macroscope spent the
last decade playing it safe,
and this shit,
it smells exactly the same.
It's all gimmick, no edge.
Which is why we should put
every chip we have into--
- Can you just,
like, shut the fuck up...
- Fuck Seattle.
...for five seconds?
Please, man.
- [Darryl] And fuck grunge.
- Jesus Christ.
Jenny,
people still wanna dance, baby.
They also wanna feel something
fresh, something real, Darryl.
[chuckles]
What about Artillery?
Wanda.
Who is this?
My intern.
How many times
I gotta tell you,
that self-righteous Blood
ain't worth the fleas
he's infested in?
Artillery rings a bell.
Refresh my memory.
He's a wild motherfucker.
He just dropped that song
called "Officer Blackman,"
about the cop who got killed
a few weeks ago.
That's right.
Guess we can call
that artistic license, huh?
Wait, wait,
so what are you saying?
You ain't afraid of the optics?
What I'm saying
is he's interesting.
Actually, he's exactly
the kind of edge we need
to cut through this bullshit.
- Can you get him?
- I can close anybody, Jenny.
We'd have to
feature him on your label,
under us, of course.
Oh.
You'd do that for me, huh?
We take the heat.
Y'all get the money.
I think the smart play
would be to give
my client a production deal
up-front, Ms. Favreau.
No way.
No way do we preemptively
offer that to a rap act.
That rap act had white kids
coming down from Pasadena
to South Central
just to see him perform.
That's what you're paying for.
[Darryl] Wanda.
Listen, Jenny,
pimp me, pay me...
I'm good.
Bring me Artillery
with a new song,
then we can talk
about a production deal.
Make sure
to bring this one too.
I know. You had everything
under control, and I panicked.
Next time,
I'll watch and learn, promise.
Since you're so obsessed
with him...
find out where Artillery
is going to be at tonight.
I'm gonna hook
that uppity hobo.
[♪ tense music plays]
Okay. Done.
- [Darryl chuckles]
- [♪ music ends]
[♪ hip-hop playing]
[no audible dialogue]
[police officer 1] There he is.
Mr. Cop Killer himself.
[♪ hip-hop playing on radio]
[♪ music ends]
[Darryl] My boys are already
here, on point as usual.
As long as you keep
that sexy-ass mouth closed,
we winning.
Then let me speak
my piece right now.
DG, Artillery is not like you.
Smirk all you want,
but I know how to read men.
He is an artist.
[♪ hip-hop playing]
[♪ music stops]
[sighs]
[♪ hip-hop playing]
[♪ music stops]
Can we end this bullshit, please?
- [♪ music stops]
- [sighs]
Look, man, I already
told you this, all right?
We already got a deal set up.
All we need
is a demo now, my nigga,
then we could figure out
- whatever sound it is
that you want, baby.
- [Artillery] Hey!
Don't call me nigga, man.
Nigga man.
Nigga man, nigga man. [scoffs]
Nigger.
Nigga.
Man.
[Artillery scoffs]
You hate me, huh?
Your taste in music
exposes you, Blood.
You a vulture.
Look, I-I cannot
be your carcass, sir.
I'd rather die in my hood, get
picked apart by family cluckers
than you and
Bob Dole. [scoffs]
[Leonard] That's...
- Look, fellas--
- Shut the fuck up, Vance.
What's it gonna take
for me to make you rich?
Help me walk on water, nigga.
Eve is all of y'all's mama.
Everyone next to you
would care, including
the people you fucked,
so all I'm asking is...
A lot of people you kill,
'cause they you too.
How did you even hear that?
I heard
every song you ever made,
including those first demos.
[Artillery] Do I know you?
No.
I know what I felt
when I first heard you.
It was the same as when
I was getting clean and God
lifted me up out of my body.
I've seen it all, and you...
something special.
But the last Black man to walk
on water was nailed to a cross.
So let me help you
find the right music
before that happens.
You got a week.
I had to do it.
I guess sleeping
on the couch is one hell
of a motivator, huh?
[scoffs]
You know,
when he was all up on you.
I ain't like that shit.
I know.
You really aren't coming in?
[scoffs] Not dressed like this.
You know,
Big Daddy got his rules.
I ain't trying to be looking
like Ward Cleaver every day.
Besides, after two years
of these meetings,
hood ain't getting
no better, so...
[person whistles]
Lamar tell you he turned down
that seat with our band?
[♪ piano playing]
[chattering]
[♪ gentle music playing]
So you ain't taking
the job at First AME?
[♪ music stops]
[♪ jazzy music playing]
[Big Daddy] What happened?
[♪ music ends]
Stupid-ass bullshit, man.
[sighs]
- [Big Daddy]
Now, what was that all about?
- Fuck, man.
[James] Look, I can't
enlist no more, all right?
I'm staying with Lamar.
We talked about this. That's
exactly what you gonna do.
You gonna enlist,
and that boy's gonna
play for the church.
Well, Lamar turned down the job
at First AME.
He did what?
[sighs]
Boy, what did you do?
What did I do?
I didn't do shit, man.
Yo...
You can keep trying to blame me
for everything,
but you can't stop
that little nigga from...
Don't you ever, ever use
that word about your brother.
He almost got himself killed
the other day by the 80s.
I'm the one
who went and got him.
I'm the one who saved him, man.
What's your plan now?
Okay.
Back inside, all right?
Don't make a scene.
I'm good.
[♪ hip-hop playing]
[♪ music ends]
[Gerty] Wanda, let's just talk
about this tomorrow.
Look, I'm just asking
for an open mind.
Macroscope's the real deal.
This could be huge for Lamar.
And you.
Come on, I mean,
sure, b-but we both know
he wants this.
You understand
everything that's happening
with these boys right now?
I got a tinderbox, and you keep
trying to sell me matches.
Sell you?
I'm not walking around here
sneaking like the Hamburglar.
Look, Lamar's my family too,
and I ain't gonna let anything
happen to him.
You are my other child,
and I'm telling you,
Wanda, as family...
no.
[water running]
Mama G,
is it me?
God gave this to me when
I was in Africa, this plan.
[Gerty] Then it'll happen.
Without Lamar.
[engine cranking]
[grunts] Fuck!
Look, I say that to say
people don't doubt your dreams
because of who you were.
All right?
They doubt 'em because
dreams just ain't reality.
I ain't accepting
that blue-collar news, Lee.
We had to run to Africa
to get away from these streets,
and now you're climbing
through windows,
lying to your family,
trying to chase every D-Boy
who survived a dope game
into this music bullshit?
See? That's the shit that got
you cut in the first place.
I don't know why
we broke up, anyway.
Africa changed us, Lee.
I found myself and...
you became more stubborn...
[scoffs] ...use that
as a buffer.
- Wanda, stop, all right?
- [chuckles]
I could see the road
you're headed down, and
the shit is gonna end bad...
- Fuck you.
- ...all right?
See?
Nah, fuck you.
Quit your damn legal clinic
and give me the money
so I could start
my music label like I asked
your ass before I joined DG.
Stop fucking playing with me.
Nah, you casually telling me
I can't do shit.
And fuck you
for not wanting to do shit.
And fuck Big Daddy
and Mama G ass for snuffing
that boy's dreams out
to protect him against
the shit you and Franklin
and the rest
of these same gangsters
did to me and these streets.
I'm sorry, Lee,
but you want the truth, right?
I need to give up, right?
So if you want the truth,
did I lie?
No, you're right.
We tore this whole shit up
and survived all the funerals,
me and you.
Nobody else.
And now you're gonna
walk Lamar straight into
that same buzz saw.
And when he get hurt,
which he will,
what's that gonna do
to you, huh?
Look, I-I don't want this
between me and you, all right?
All this
back and forth and shit,
us not being cohesive.
Let me take care of you until
you can figure out another w--
[gunshots]
[tires squeal]
Hey, let's go get in the car.
[dogs barking in distance]
[helicopter whirring
in distance]
Okay.
This whole fucking city
is gonna eat us alive.
[♪ hip-hop playing]
[Lamar] Fuck.
James was fucking right.
There's too much decay
on this 808.
I-I thought it was
gonna go with the synth,
but it's just a fucking--
Lamar, why is
your fine-ass cousin standing
outside the window?
- [♪ music stops]
- What the fuck?
[Lamar sighs]
- [Lamar grunts]
- [creaking]
Shit.
- What-What are you doing here?
- Shh.
Turn it back up
so they don't hear me.
[sighs]
- Hey, Wanda.
- [♪ music resumes]
I need you to make a track
for me. Something special.
What?
[sighs] Your ass took a job
- with Pastor Rodney?
- I had to for James.
[Wanda] Listen, Lamar, this
is one of those moments, man.
This isn't about James
or Big Daddy or Mama G.
This is about you.
If you shrink,
there's nobody to blame.
What do you want?
Shit ain't that simple, Wanda.
Do you know
who this track is for?
[Lamar] No.
[♪ music ends]
- Who?
- [scoffs]
Artillery.
Artillery?
Oh, shit. Lamar,
you gotta do it. [chuckles]
Are you... Are you serious?
You're being for real?
[Wanda]
This is what I'm thinking.
Holy shit. Yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes.
Underrated baseline.
And it's hella Black.
What if you looped the horns?
I love that.
If we loop these horns,
it gives the baseline time
- to cycle
until it resets. Yeah.
- Right? Right?
The horns will keep it hip-hop
so the funk don't dominate
at the same time, Lamar,
at the same motherfucking time.
This is not New York City
brick building shit.
This is Hennessy
and a card game, baby.
We got to bring Artillery
some real player shit.
[♪ "The Cisco Kid" plays]
[sirens wailing]
[person 5] One time, one time!
♪ The Cisco Kid
Was a friend of mine ♪
[person 5]
You better watch your back.
Five-O, Five-O.
Let's get him. Hey, yo.
Pump on the box. Get him!
You soft motherfuckers.
♪ The outlaws had us
Pinned down at the fort ♪
♪ Cisco came in blastin'
Drinkin' port ♪
Got you down, motherfucker.
♪ Cisco came in blastin'
Drinkin' port ♪
Wait, who's this?
[grunts]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[groans]
♪ The Cisco Kid
Was a friend of mine ♪
[grunts]
[groaning]
You make songs
about killing one of my men?
- [Artillery groans]
- Hmm?
I gotta hear about this garbage
at the memorial.
[sirens wailing]
We got outside eyes coming.
[Artillery groans]
[police officer 2] Throw
this motherfucker in the car.
He's going on a field trip.
[police officer 3] Let it go.
It's just a song.
How do we look at our men
if we let this go?
Put him in my car.
I'll dump him in Tannerhood and
let the Crips deal with him.
[♪ hip-hop playing]
[Wanda] If I'm gonna bring the
only family I got into this,
- Darryl, you gotta
make me a partner...
- [♪ music ends]
...at least on this record.
Did you hear what I said?
[phone ringing]
Darryl,
deep down,
more than you wanna fuck me,
you know I got vision.
Stop pretending
that shit ain't real. Make me
a partner on this record.
I brought you Lamar.
My money, my name, my connects.
- I will burn
this deal the fuck down.
- It's business, Wanda.
I can break you off,
but I can't make you-- Girl!
[muffled groaning]
- The fuck is you doing?
- [Wanda] Fuck you!
You done fucked up now!
My people
are gonna fuck you up!
That was BY. Bad news.
Artillery's dead.
[siren wailing]
[line ringing]
[Lamar] Hello?
Where the fuck you going?
[Lamar] Uh...
Nowhere.
- I-I'll be right back.
- Hey, don't make me
park your little ass.
Where you going?
Wanda, uh...
Wanda was on the phone.
She said Artillery
ain't-ain't dead.
She said that, uh,
his family just said that
so that nobody
would come to the hospital
to finish the job, but...
apparently he didn't get out
even an hour ago, so...
[James] So what, nigga?
What, you think I'm finna let
you and your female cousin go
to a house full of Bloods after
they top trophy been shut?
At night?
[scoffs]
Nigga, that's preposterous.
Sit your ass down.
Fuck you, James.
[chuckles]
What?
I said fuck you.
[James scoffs]
So, it's... it's like that?
It's like that.
Yo, why is everything
around here pressure to be
like everything around here?
You pressure too.
Bro, I'm trying
to imagine my music floating
out of car windows,
and you're in my head
shutting me down.
Our grandparents
will damn near have a stroke
if I'm out past midnight.
And these... and these
Jheri curl clones, they
think I'm a freak 'cause...
'cause I listen
to Miriam Makeba.
Y'all don't get it.
Why the fuck can't anyone
be special around here?
[James sighs]
Okay.
Okay?
[James] Yeah, man.
You know, I'm never going to
know what I could have been...
'cause I ain't never did
no shit like this.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, you...
Not-Not for what
you believe in.
Cuz,
I ain't even know you had
this type of shit in you.
You gotta understand, though,
if you go down this road,
you're going to see a different
side of Big Daddy and Gert.
You know that, right?
I can't not do this.
Fuck.
Let's go, bro.
I like this. This feels good.
- [shouting on tape]
- [siren wailing on tape]
[giggles]
- [vocalist] You motherfucker!
- [gunfire on tape]
[vocalist 2] Got him.
[♪ "Gangsta Gangsta" plays]
♪ Never should've been
Let out the penitentiary ♪
♪ Ice Cube would like to say ♪
- Hey, we ready.
- Hey, what's good, yo?
Let's get up in here.
[James]
Goddamn, I didn't even know
there's so many Bloods in LA.
[hammer cocks]
Y'all wait here till I say.
♪ To a kid lookin' up to me ♪
♪ Life ain't nothin'
But bitches and money ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the type of nigga
That's built to last ♪
♪ See, I don't give a fuck
'Cause I keep bailin' ♪
♪ Yo, what the fuck
Are they yellin'? ♪
♪ Gangsta, Gangsta!
That's what they're yellin' ♪
♪ It's not about a salary
It's all about reality ♪
♪♪ Hopin' you
Sophisticated motherfuckers ♪
♪♪ 'Cause you know
They know what's up ♪
Hey, Dara.
♪♪ Like her
But she keep cryin' ♪
- ♪ I got a boyfriend ♪
- ♪ Bitch, stop lyin' ♪
♪ Dumb-ass hooker ain't nothin'
But a dyke ♪
♪ Suddenly I see some niggas
That I don't like ♪
♪ Walked over to 'em, and said
"What's up?" ♪
♪ The first nigga that I saw
Hit him in the jaw ♪
Sorry, he's too fucked up
to come out
and now's a bad time, so...
Shit. All right. Just give 'em
the tape, and let's slide.
Can we... Just hold on.
Can we get, like, just two
minutes to play it for him?
The fuck are you doing?
I mean, you can, but if
these fools start trippin',
I don't know what to tell you.
Just like two minutes, I swear.
Come hang by Tunk,
so shit stay cool.
Stay next to me.
[♪ "This Is for the Lover
In You" playing]
♪♪ For the lover in you ♪
- ♪♪ This ring means
I'll always be true ♪
- ♪ Always be true ♪
- Will you shut
the fuck up already?
- No.
♪♪ This time ♪
♪♪ Is gonna last forever ♪
This fool. What's up, man?
Oh, you don't remember me now?
Nah, bro.
Tip-Toe, nigga.
- Oh, yeah. What's up, homie?
- Hey.
Hey, OG, this is that fool
that gave me a pass
that time I got caught slipping
in the gates.
I don't care
about that bullshit.
♪♪ I can say
I never met a girl, no, no ♪
♪♪ Who satisfied my mental
And my physical thing ♪
The fuck you going?
Actually, I was, uh, hoping
I could play it for Artillery.
- [Dara] Nah.
- [door closes]
You, like, his manager, right?
- Sure.
- And his family too, right?
Uh...
Ain't no moves with me, Wanda.
Now y'all need to go
before shit pops off.
I don't give a fuck about no
rap shit. These motherfuckers
shouldn't be here.
Matter of fact, where the fuck
you from, Blood, huh?
Hey, hey,
hey, hey. Hey, look...
We ain't want none of that.
Hey, wait a sec. Key.
[gangster 1]
I don't give a fuck
about none of that shit.
I'll get on you
right now, nigga.
What, nigga?
Be cool, all right?
[gangster 1]
Nigga, you heard me.
The fuck you from?
Don't start with that shit.
- All right.
Just calm down, nigga.
- [clicks]
- [gangster 1]
We gonna get you, nigga.
- What was that?
[♪ hip-hop playing]
What the fuck is he doing?
Shh.
- [gangster 2]
Turn that shit up.
- [Artillery] Hey, Blood.
Hey, big homie.
Hey, run that shit back.
[gangster 2] Hey, yo heard.
[cassette rewinding]
[♪ hip-hop playing]
♪ Oh, yeah
You gonna respect my get down ♪
♪ Sawed-off 12 gauge make
The biggest nigga sit down ♪
♪♪ Demons lurking down
They putting work
They never clock out ♪
♪ Fuck, I just heard the Feds
Hit my uncle Roc house ♪
♪ Pushing up Central
Head on the swivel ♪
♪ Chronic in that eight ball
Stabilize the mental ♪
♪ Brothers dropping brothers
Just to get a name ♪
♪ Desensitized from the pain
The streets wild and untamed ♪
♪♪ I see a bust
Or another target
Slip in front of his building ♪
♪ Fuck, they shoot off
The whole apartment ♪
♪ Mark, system may seem
Deceiving to save a few souls ♪
♪ Gotta drop a few demons
Oh, Jesus, nigga ♪
♪♪ These are life
And times of a rider
Life and times of a rider ♪
♪ Survival is vital
These are life and times
Of a rider ♪
♪ And motherfuck
The other siders, yeah ♪
♪♪ These are
Life and times of a rider
Life and times of a rider ♪
[gangster 3] Yeah, Blood.
♪♪ These are
Life and times of a rider and
Motherfuck the other siders ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪♪ These are
Life and times of a rider
The life and times of a rider ♪
♪♪ These are life
And times of a rider and
Motherfuck the other siders ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪♪ These are
Life and times of a rider
The life and times of a rider ♪
[♪ "m.A.A.d city" plays]